<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<feed xmlns="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
    <id>https://courtneychow88.github.io</id>
    <title>Courtney Chow</title>
    <updated>2019-11-15T05:37:40.018Z</updated>
    <generator>https://github.com/jpmonette/feed</generator>
    <link rel="alternate" href="https://courtneychow88.github.io"/>
    <link rel="self" href="https://courtneychow88.github.io/atom.xml"/>
    <subtitle>善终如始。</subtitle>
    <logo>https://courtneychow88.github.io/images/avatar.png</logo>
    <icon>https://courtneychow88.github.io/favicon.ico</icon>
    <rights>All rights reserved 2019, Courtney Chow</rights>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[😇A Relaxation Method Daily😇]]></title>
        <id>https://courtneychow88.github.io/post/a-relaxation-method-daily</id>
        <link href="https://courtneychow88.github.io/post/a-relaxation-method-daily">
        </link>
        <updated>2018-12-14T14:47:12.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[<p>While we are woring with others, the very often questions or complains we got from others might be:&quot;Hey, can you controll your temper?&quot;,or simply feel dislike from people around you.</p>
]]></summary>
        <content type="html"><![CDATA[<p>While we are woring with others, the very often questions or complains we got from others might be:&quot;Hey, can you controll your temper?&quot;,or simply feel dislike from people around you.</p>
<!-- more -->
<p>Being a Product Manager, leadership does not actually comes from your tile but the respect from your team members. Maybe the first thing you need to do is Temper Controlling.<br>
I learnt these things from an HBR article, written by <em>Daniel Goleman</em>. Helps<br>
me a lot when I got to face the dark side of me.</p>
<p><em>Manage your reaction:</em></p>
<p><em>Keep your distaste to yourself</em></p>
<ul>
<li>No complain to others</li>
<li>Keep your support connections outside the office<br>
<em>Consider whether it’s you, not them</em></li>
<li>“Start with the hypothesis that the person is doing things you don’t like but is a good person,”</li>
<li>By better understanding what is bothering you, you may also be able to see your role in it.<br>
<em>Spend more time with them</em></li>
<li>Develop some empathy<br>
<em>Consider providing feedback</em></li>
<li>Focus on behaviors that she can control and describe how they impact you and your work together.</li>
<li>But proceed cautiously<br>
<em>Adopt a don’t-care attitude</em></li>
<li>“practice the fine art of emotional detachment or not giving a shit.”</li>
</ul>
<p><em>Principles to Remember</em></p>
<p><em>Do:</em></p>
<ul>
<li>Manage your own reaction to the behavior first</li>
<li>Practice emotional detachment so the person’s behaviors don’t bother you</li>
<li>Spend time trying to get to know the person and better understand what motivates him</li>
</ul>
<p><em>Don’t:</em></p>
<ul>
<li>Assume that it is all about the other person — you likely play some part</li>
<li>Commiserate with others who could be unfairly influenced by your negativity or may judge you for your complaints</li>
<li>Give feedback unless you can focus on work issues and can avoid a personal conflict</li>
</ul>
]]></content>
    </entry>
</feed>